<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Terminal</title><link>https://example.com/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Terminal</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AEO Keyword Win for a Global Data Leader</title><link>https://example.com/projects/aeo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/projects/aeo/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="case-study-1-aeo-optimization-for-global-data-leader">Case Study 1: AEO Optimization for Global Data Leader&lt;/h2>
&lt;h4 id="achieving-position-3--ai-overview-feature-in-2-weeks">Achieving Position 3 &amp;amp; AI Overview Feature in 2 Weeks&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>A well-known global leader in redistribution of pricing and reference data needed to establish thought leadership around economic analysis. They wanted to capture high-intent search traffic for users seeking guidance on economic evaluation methodologies, and then guide them towards their economic data consultancy offerings.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="strategy">Strategy&lt;/h1>
&lt;h2 id="phase-1-technical-seo-foundation">Phase 1: Technical SEO Foundation&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Before developing new content, I carried out a sweeping technical SEO audit that brought forward a few critical issues that would undermine (and already were undermining) the client&amp;rsquo;s search performance. These needed quick resolution to make sure any new content strategy would be successful.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Bookings for client in counselling spacee</title><link>https://example.com/projects/therapy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/projects/therapy/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="case-study-3-site-build-seo--cro-for-service-based-client">Case Study 3: Site build, SEO + CRO for service-based client&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A counselling and therapy practitioner specialising in gestalt therapy through online and in-person consultations reached out for help with her visibility. Despite being highly qualified and having a range of services already on offer, she was struggling to generate any consultations through her website, which at the time was a static, one-page website that provided basic service information but with limited to no visibility in search results.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Clustering keyword strategy for high-growth</title><link>https://example.com/projects/elearning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/projects/elearning/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="case-study-2-elearning-course-site">Case Study 2: Elearning Course Site&lt;/h2>
&lt;h4 id="from-27k-to-7k-monthly-clicks-through-strategic-content-silos">From 2.7K to 7K Monthly Clicks Through Strategic Content Silos&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>An eLearning platform specializing in responsive design courses for web and UX designers was struggling with visibility beyond their branded searches. Their traffic was heavily concentrated on course pages and brand match queries, which had worked well enough so far, but they were missing smart opportunities to capture users through earlier stages of their learning journey, primarily through informational queries that signalled interest or awareness in topics related to the client&amp;rsquo;s courses.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>